Three female ghosts.
Come out yourselves.
Inspector Mu.
We did the killing and played the ghosts.
It doesn't involve Chunmei and the rest.
You three are from the Acrobatic troupe.
All of you,
Explain yourselves right now.
Who is the real killer?
Who exactly are you people?
Do you still remember
this house?
Whose home was it two years ago?
Chunmei!
What's wrong, Chunmei?
Erzhu!
Are you okay, Erzhu?
Kids, don't panic.
Quickly cover her mouth and nose.
Come.
Hurry, cover her mouth and nose.
Let's go. Come home with me.
Hold her steady.
Come on.
Erzhu.
This way.
Come.
Here.
We're home. We're home.
Help her sit down quickly.
Grandpa.
Who are they?
They inhaled Miasma in the mountains.
Boil some water quickly.
Grandpa will clear their poison.
Come on, help her sit down.
Okay.
Chunmei.
Little sister.
Sister, take your medicine.
Here.
Feeling better?
You'll be fine.
Weren't we in the mountains?
Where are we?
Here's what happened.
You guys...
Lucky I was picking herbs up here.
There's Miasma on this mountain.
You were all poisoned by the Miasma.
You barely made it out alive.
Thank you.
Thank you for saving our lives, Doctor.
Alright, alright.
Come on, sit down quickly.
Come, come.
You didn't know.
Lijia Town is deep in the mountains.
There's Miasma on this mountain.
Even the hunters from our own town
don't dare go up there to hunt.
Looking at you siblings,
you must be from out of town, right?
There's a war in the north,
so we had to flee south.
My eldest brother is a factory guard.
Nice to meet you.
I'm a worker at a chemical plant.
And this is my little sister.
She works at a textile mill.
These days,
with all the chaos of war,
it's much more peaceful here in the mountains.
How about this?
You siblings
can stay with me for the time being.
You see,
It's just me and my little grandson here.
It gets pretty lonely.
Having you siblings to keep me company
would make me very happy.
Well...
Wouldn't that be an imposition?
My eldest brother can do carpentry,
my second brother can grow flowers,
and I can do needlework.
So please let us stay.
Let us repay you for saving our lives.
There's no need for repayment.
I told you, Xiao Bao,
that's my acupuncture dummy,
not your toy.
Look, you broke it again!
It's fine, Benefactor.
I know carpentry.
I'll make you a new one later.
I'd appreciate that. Thank you.
Hurry up!
Move faster, all of you!
Did you hear me?
Hurry up!
I said hurry up! Faster!
Little sister!
Have some pity.
Please give us a bite to eat.
We're tired and hungry.
We really can't walk anymore.
You want food?
Stop wasting my food!
Once we get to town,
I'm going to sell every single one of you!
Little bastards!
Hurry up!
Move!
Move it!
Don't be afraid, kids.
Hurry, come with me.
Look at this.
When writing this stroke,
do it like this.
We were homeless,
but Elder Ding took us all in.
We finally had a home.
Careful, don't fall.
Grandpa rescued us from
those human traffickers.
From now on, he's our real Grandpa.
We have a family now, too.
We'll never have to go hungry again.
Grandpa, I'll stay with you forever.
Our Lijia Town
is a poor place.
You three sisters
are just at the right age to study.
By the way,
take this money with you.
Go learn some skills in the city.
Grandpa is getting old,
and I don't have much to teach you.
You three sisters
can't waste away in this thatched hut.
It just so happens
I have an old friend from my hometown
who runs an Acrobatic troupe in the city.
I've already written him a letter.
Acrobatics?
You'll go to his place,
and from now on,
you can learn the trade while studying.
Acrobatics?
What's that?
Well, acrobatics
is the art of body flexibility.
As long as you learn it well,
you'll not only build your physique,
and be able to support yourselves.
Interesting!
I want to learn acrobatics in the city.
Grandpa,
once we've learned the skills,
we'll come back and see you.
Alright.
Then it's a promise.
Okay.
Come on, hurry up and eat.
Here, eat while it's hot.
Okay.
Take care on your journey.
Let's go.
Elder Ding used all his savings
to send the sisters to study in the city.
The three of us who stayed behind
helped take care of Xiao Bao,
and worked odd jobs to support the family.
We were poor, but happy.
Until that day...
Benefactor Li came looking for us.
What are you doing?
I'm a Doctor.
Healing and saving lives is my duty.
I can't accept this consultation fee.
This isn't a medical fee.
It's money to buy your land.
I want this piece of land.
Take Xiao Bao and move out immediately.
Why would you say that?
I'm the only Doctor in this town.
If I leave,
who will treat the people here?
If you leave, a new Doctor will come.
You could practice medicine all your life
and never earn this much money.
Just take it.
Xiao Bao.
This is for you.
It's made of nanmu wood.
It won't break.
Thank you, Brother Dazhu.
Now I can watch puppet shows every day!
Do you like it?
Good boy.
Xiao Bao, who is that?
He passed out at our door.
He had a knife wound.
Grandpa healed him.
Benefactor Li, please see yourself out.
Take it.
I really can't take it.
You old fool!
Don't push your luck!
Let me tell you,
I'm getting this land no matter what.
Just you wait.
See yourself out.
A knife wound?
Yeah, a knife wound.
Grandpa.
What do they want?
They're so fierce.
Don't mind them.
He wants us to move out,
but I don't want to.
Brother Dazhu even specially
made me a puppet toy.
Look.
Very nice, very nice.
Come, let's go inside.
Elder Ding and Xiao Bao not only saved us,
they saved you too.
How could you be so cruel to them?
You tied Xiao Bao up for the river god,
as a human foundation sacrifice.